<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reversance blog</title>
    <link>https://www.reversance.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Reversance blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 12:33:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.reversance.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing and using TWRP Recovery for Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 MTK</title>
      <link>https://www.reversance.com/2017/05/30/installing-and-using-twrp-recovery-for-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-mtk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 12:33:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.reversance.com/2017/05/30/installing-and-using-twrp-recovery-for-xiaomi-redmi-note-4-mtk/</guid>
      <description>In the last post I have presented you way of unlocking bootloader in Xiaomi Redmi Note 4. Now it is the time to install custom Recovery Image and use it to flash your desired ROM. Remember that to follow this instructions you need to have unlocked bootloader.
Warning  Custom recovery image will allow you to make deep modifications in your phone software. This includes complete remove of Android operation system (don&amp;rsquo;t worry it can be installed again).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redmi Note 4 MTK Bootloader Unlocking using Linux</title>
      <link>https://www.reversance.com/2017/05/11/redmi-note-4-mtk-bootloader-unlocking-using-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 16:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.reversance.com/2017/05/11/redmi-note-4-mtk-bootloader-unlocking-using-linux/</guid>
      <description>After long and tedious process of unlocking bootloader in my Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 phone using linux, to sum up I decided to write definitive tutorial about it. I have collected all informations that were scattered around internet and gathered them in one place.
Note This tutorial is written especially for MTK SOC devices, so if you have locked bootlader on other Xiaomi phone that Redmi Note 4 and it is MTK, then you can try unlocking it using tools and methods presented here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So I end up creating blog... - Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://www.reversance.com/2017/04/20/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.reversance.com/2017/04/20/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello! This is my first post on my new blog. I hope it will be intresting site for everyone. I will mainly write about computer science related topics, but sometimes there will be post about something else.
I hope that I will stay motivated to lead this blog as long as possible.
Have nice day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.reversance.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.reversance.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my blog site. I would like to encourage you to look around and explore it.
About me My name is Radek and I am currently studying Computer Science at Master&amp;rsquo;s academic degree. My main interests include programming in various languages and reverse engineering. I use arch linux at every day basis. I have big experience working with various Linux distributions such as:
 debian ubuntu redhat arch  I created this blog to establish my Computer Science knowledge and share my thoughts and experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.reversance.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.reversance.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me using followig ways:
 github bitbucket email: r&amp;hellip;@reversance.com  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>